你究竟在想在这儿干嘛
What the hell were you trying to do in there?
你不能像这样逼病人
You do not push a patient like that.
我只是...  我希望我能够...
I just -- I hoped that I could --
干嘛  催着她想起来吗
What, that you could badger her into remembering?
事不是这样做的
That is not how this works.
她今天已经够糟心了
She was distressed enough already,
你现在只是让她过得更糟心
And you are only making it worse.
谢博德医生  你应该停止
Dr. Shepherd, you can stop yelling
在走廊吼我的住院医师
at my resident in the hallway.
你的住院医师  你的住院医师
Your resident? Your resident?
是的  没错  她今天是我的住院医师
Yes, yes, today she's my resident.
我想吼谁就吼谁  你管不着
Okay, I can yell at any resident I want to,
何况她还折磨了我的病人
especially if she has been tormenting my patient.
这样就太不专业了
It looks completely unprofessional.
你真的想和我吵这个
You really want to argue about this?
听着  事实上  是的  因为你已经
Listen -- I do, actually, because you have been
彻头彻尾的不可理喻了
totally unreasonable at every level.
而且你现在完全越界了
And you are completely out of line.
听着  行吗
Listen! Okay?